johnsonjobs.com 2015-05-16

# Terms and Privacy | Johnson Careers | Johnson Careers

## Terms and Privacy

**Johnson Careers** provides this notice to inform you about the manner in which we collect, use, disclose, retain and transfer personal information. 

#### INFORMATION WE COLLECT.

 **Johnson Careers** collects personal information (e.g. name, e-mail address, physical address, telephone number), resume information (e.g. employment history, education, professional credentials), and other information acquired through our services, for example, information provided when you register to use our services, submit a resume, respond to employment opportunities, take assessments, provide information about other assessment participants, or contact us. We also may collect sensitive information (e.g. gender, race, age, nationality) in certain cases, including through optional demographic survey questions. Except in these limited cases, we encourage you not to provide other sensitive information to us. 

#### HOW WE USE THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT.

We use the information we collect in support of our services, including to respond to your inquiries and fulfill your requests; to render services to our clients; for business purposes, such as data analysis, identification of usage trends, internal communication regarding candidates and clients, improvement of our services, and financial transactions; to send e-mails, articles, and other marketing information regarding **Johnson Careers** services; to invite participation in online surveys; and to provide administrative information regarding changes to our terms, conditions, and policies. We also use personal information to identify professional opportunities and contact candidates regarding such opportunities. We may also aggregate and disclose diversity statistics regarding our candidates and placement activities. We may use de-identified or aggregate data for any purpose including to generate norms, conduct ongoing validation studies, compile reports, conduct ongoing research, and to develop new products and services. 

#### DISCLOSURE TO CLIENTS, SERVICE PROVIDERS AND OTHERS.

 **Johnson Careers** may disclose personal information, including assessment results and related data, to clients that have engaged our services and prospective employers that have engaged **Johnson Careers** to fulfill search requests. 

#### OTHER INFORMATION WE COLLECT.

 **Johnson Careers** collects certain other information that does not reveal your specific identity. If you visit our websites, we use cookies, pixel tags, and other technologies to perform statistical analyses of the collective characteristics and behavior of our website visitors, measure demographics and interest in specific areas of our website, retrieve usernames and passwords, measure the success of our communications, and compile statistics about website usage and response rates. 

#### CHOICE AND ACCESS.

Providing personal information to us is voluntary, although if you do not provide certain personal information you may not be able to participate in our services. You may contact us at privacy@johnsoncareers.com if you wish to ask how we handle personal information, obtain a copy of such information, review, correct or update your personal information, or request that your personal information be removed from our database. If you wish to opt-out of receiving messages from us, you can follow the unsubscribe instructions within all email communication from Johnson Careers. 

By accepting below, you acknowledge that Johnson Careers may send you marketing materials by email. If you wish to opt-out of receiving marketing messages from us, you can follow the unsubscribe instructions that are contained in each email sent by Johnson Careers. 

#### SECURITY.

 **Johnson Careers** has implemented reasonable organizational, technical and administrative measures to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of personal information under our control. If you have reason to believe that your interaction with us is no longer secure, please immediately notify us of the problem. 

#### QUESTIONS.

Questions regarding this Privacy Policy should be directed to **Johnson Careers** at privacy@johnsoncareers.com 

#### ACKNOWLEDGMENT AND CONSENT

I understand that **Johnson Careers** may collect, use, transfer and disclose personal information as described in this **Johnson Careers** Privacy Policy, including both within and outside of the country in which I am based. I confirm my consent to this collection, use, transfer, and disclosure of my personal information.
